Previously on "Pretty Little Liars..."
Dr. Rollins.
I thought I'd let you know in person.
The judge set a day for the hearing.
The court can compel your friends
to come but they may not
be sympathetic to the cause.
So this court thing...
It's just about how we feel
about Charlotte getting out.
It is about A getting out.
- Five A free years.
- What are we gonna do?
You got involved in government first
and your mother is going
to be a state senator.
Your bosses are very angry at me.
They're not angry.
They gave me an advance on a second book.
They know what happened in South America.
College wasn't what I
thought it was gonna be.
I had a hard time, when my dad died
I just couldn't see a point to it.
My family has always had a missing part.
What's missing is my sister, Charlotte
and now I wanna bring my sister home.
(female ♪1) 'You're here to
tell me if you'd feel safe'
should Charlotte DiLaurentis
leave the hospital?
No, I would not feel safe.
So that's that.
Judge says Charlotte can go home.
(Elly) 'Did Charlotte come to
your hotel room last night?'
- I don't know where she is.
- You don't know where she is?
We went to bed and this
morning she was gone.
(Aria) What is she doing here?
(Emily) Making sure that
Charlotte's really dead.
(Lorenzo) 'Charlotte was
dead when she was thrown'
from the bell tower. The
death's been ruled a homicide.
You'll get a call.
(Aria) When did you tell Jordan?
(Hanna) Tell him what?
This town, Charlotte
everything we went through.
She means the things she can't Google.
When I knew I was falling in love with him.
Hmm, Liam and I aren't there yet but...
I know he's gonna have a lot
of questions when I get back.
Are you sure you should leave tonight?
You know the cops wanna
talk to us before we go.
Yeah, I've already
missed a few days of work.
We all have, Aria. We're staying.
Okay, well, my boss asked me to come back.
You guys, this wasn't an easy job to get.
I can't lose it.
They're gonna ask us
questions about that night.
Yeah, we were all together
and none of us left the hotel.
What else is there to say?
I think the person the cops
should really be talking to
is right over there.
[indistinct chattering]
(Spencer) 'Can she really
not sign her own name?'
I still haven't told anyone
about what happened, have you?
Do we really believe she doesn't remember?
I think she's lying.
Just like she lied about
having Swedish Syndrome
to get her sentence reduced.
Stockholm Syndrome. And it is a real thing.
She was never kidnapped, Spencer.
She was living out in the world.
She chose to help Charlotte torture us.
You know, the judge didn't see it that way.
If Sara really was
brainwashed, she'd have a pretty
strong motive to kill Charlotte. Revenge.
Oh, I hate to break up this
party but I gotta get going.
- I'll walk you to your car.
- Okay. Bye.
- I'll call you soon.
- Okay.
- Love you.
- Love you too.
Hey, um, I didn't wanna say
anything in front of the others
but I know that you left the hotel
the night Charlotte was killed.
Where did you go?
[dramatic music]
♪ Got a secret can you keep it ♪
♪ Swear this one you'll save ♪
♪ Better lock it in your pocket ♪
♪ Taking this one to the grave ♪
♪ If I show you then I know you ♪
♪ Won't tell what I said ♪
♪ Cause two can keep a secret ♪
♪ If one of them is dead ♪
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
I got up around 3:00 a.m. to
hydrate and I saw you leave.
I had to check my messages
and, um, then my phone died
so I, I had to grab my charger from my car.
- Then what?
- I came back to the room.
You were gone longer than
that. I tried to wait up.
Hanna, you're remembering it wrong.
Which isn't a surprise
considering how wasted you got.
- Um, I wasn't that drunk.
- You threw up in a bathtub.
That was Emily, not me.
[indistinct chattering]
Look, all I'm saying is if you did
go somewhere... we should know.
Well, I didn't, so there's nothing to tell.
Okay.
I have a plane to catch.
[intense music]
[door opens]
Mom, Caleb just got here.
Already you're putting him to work?
What's wrong?
The news of Charlotte's
death is spreading fast.
Some bloggers are trying to
link you and the girls to it.
[sighs] Why am I not surprised?
I am. It's a disgusting thing to do.
My opponent is running a dirty campaign.
Well, how do you know
that she's behind this?
I'm trying to figure out
where it's coming from.
It doesn't matter. It's already out there.
And it would be a mistake
for me to go with you
to your interview tomorrow.
Why?
Because I would just be a distraction.
Honey, the "Rosewood
Observer" has more class
than to pay attention to
a few tasteless tweets.
Mom, I'm partially responsible
for Charlotte's getting out.
On the night that she did, she was killed.
So whichever way they spin it, her death
and my association to it will come up
and it's best if I'm not
with you when it does.
Hey, I found a link to a blog
that originated in Rosewood.
'It's been shared over 400 times.'
Maybe it is best if you skipped this one.
- Yeah.
- I'll call my team.
And see if they can get a handle on this.
Okay.
I am really afraid that she's gonna lose
this election because of me.
Hey, don't say that.
I'll hack into the voting machines
and make sure that she wins.
- Caleb.
- I'm kidding.
[both laughing]
Look, they have 400 retweets.
I will get 4000 good
ones by tomorrow morning.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
[mellow music]
I'm really glad that you're here.
[chuckles] Me too.
[phone ringing]
[dramatic music]
(Lorenzo) 'Alison.'
Her burns severely limit
her ability to use her hands.
She couldn't have done this.
You're taking Sara off the suspect list.
I don't understand.
Charlotte's death was violent.
There was a struggle.
You sure you wanna hear this?
I need to know what happened to my sister.
Her neck was broken by a blunt force trauma
before she was thrown from the bell tower.
I'm sorry, Alison.
We're looking at everyone but particularly
the people Charlotte targeted.
Do you think your friends
could have had anything
to do with Charlotte's death?
No, I don't.
You sure about that?
[music continues]
(Emily) 'That's great.'
9:00 works.
I'll see you in the morning. Thanks.
How was the service?
Um, Ali said some nice things
and her doctor.
- Did you go to the cemetery?
- No. Why?
Well, the DiLaurentis'
plot is close to ours, so...
No, we just left after the service.
Look, why don't you come
with me tomorrow morning?
We could water the
flowers and say hi to dad.
Yeah, 'cause I don't need to
see where he's buried to say hi.
Okay, but you haven't seen it.
And since the funeral
you haven't even seen his headstone.
I'm sorry. I can't do it tomorrow.
I promised Ali I'd be
available to her all day
and she really needs me, so...
I'm gonna take a shower.
[instrumental music]
Hi.
I'm sorry. I think you have the wrong room.
I didn't order that.
I did.
[chuckles] Jordan.
How did you...
I got the key from your mom.
I wanted to surprise you.
I thought the magazine was
going to print tomorrow.
It is but the cops wanna talk to you
and that trumps work for me.
How are you?
I'm better now that you're here.
♪ I'll use you as a warning sign... ♪
Champagne? What are we celebrating?
Us.
I spoke to my uncle and
he has agreed to let us
have the estate for the wedding.
In the Hamptons?
Wow, that's
amazing but...
I'm not rushing you but...
I had to come here with some good news.
I'm sorry, it's just...
Between Charlotte's
death and the cops circling us
I feel like I'm in a time warp.
I don't want you to worry about that, okay?
I spoke to my mom's lawyer.
He has agreed to come down here
go to station with you.
That's really not necessary.
I know how the cops have
treated you in the past
and we shouldn't take any chances.
Maybe we should just go
back to New York tonight.
Hanna, once the cops talk to you
and realize you had
nothing to do with this...
It will all be over.
I just want this day to be over.
Well, just because you had a bad day...
Doesn't mean it has to end that way.
Fettuccine from Balthazar.
[chuckles]
Frisee salad from Dean and DeLuca.
'And... a red velvet cupcake'
from the Greenwich Bakery.
[chuckles]
♪ And I found love
♪ When it wasn't supposed to be... ♪
Aria, hey. Uh, come in.
Uh, I only have a minute.
I'm on my way to the airport. I just...
[sighs] I just needed to stop by
and clear the air before I leave.
[door closes]
We didn't see each other the
night that Charlotte was killed.
You didn't call me. I
didn't leave the hotel.
We didn't walk or talk or go anywhere.
Understood?
Whatever you say, Aria.
[dramatic music]
(female ♪2) That hurt?
No. I've just never been
really good with needles.
Oh, you'll get used to them.
The injections too.
So are you in school or working?
Um, work... and school.
I've a couple classes
left before I graduate.
Just hold that there, please.
So you're going to, uh, Hollis?
Oh, no. Pepperdine.
I'm actually in San Diego
now though... for work.
Well, you live in California
but you're doing your treatments here?
Is that bad?
Travel puts a lot of stress on the body.
It's really best if you complete
your treatments in one place.
- Will that be a problem?
- No. No problem.
I just, I really need this to work.
Oh, I'm sure everything will be fine.
Well, see you tomorrow, okay?
[dramatic music]
(Spencer) '"The flower
was placed in her hand'
"to make it look like a suicide.
"Her fingernails were wiped clean.
So were her hands."
I'm so sorry, Ali.
Who would do something like this?
Sara Harvey.
Well, the police can't see
how she could push someone off
a building when she can barely hold a fork.
- Maybe she's lying about that.
- Or maybe she had help.
Either way, they took
her off the suspect list.
- Aria left town quickly.
- She had to go back to work.
Well, she was still angry with Charlotte.
She wasn't angry. She was scared.
And she said everything that she needed
to say up on that stand.
I saw her dad this morning.
He said that she left town
one day earlier than planned.
[intense music]
I was hoping that you guys
would come to dinner tonight.
Emily, Caleb. Jordan too.
I could really use the company.
It's been really lonely in that house.
Sure.
[mellow music]
What should we bring?
[phone ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
Welcome back, Montgomery.
Good morning, Mr. Greene.
Staff meeting. Two minutes.
Be right there.
Mm. God, I missed you.
I missed you too.
And this.
- What work?
- Yeah, work.
Boston. Normalcy.
Yeah, I still can't believe what happened.
Aria, are you okay?
Are-are you freaked out?
No, I'm okay. Kinda freaked out.
But mainly I'm just glad
to get back to regular life.
Oh, we should get to that meeting.
Yeah, we-we should.
Oh, how was Ezra Fitz?
- Did you talk to him?
- Briefly.
He's thinking about
giving back that advance.
Oh, Jillian's not gonna like that.
No, she won't.
[machine beeping]
What?
- Is it broken?
- Um, yeah, yeah.
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe.
You're Emily, right?
This thing can be finicky sometimes.
Let me try.
[machine whirrs]
I'm sorry, I don't have
any cash on me right now...
Not a problem. Really.
Thank you.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine. Thank you.
So what should we take to Alison's? Sushi?
The only tuna you're gonna find
in this town is out of a can.
Then I guess Thai food is
out of the question too?
Unless you wanna go back to New York.
If we leave now, we can make
an 8 o'clock reservation.
Are you worried about spending
the night with Alison...
Or introducing me to Caleb?
Both.
I will be on my best behavior, okay?
Alright, keep the conversation
light and we'll leave
right after after we eat.
Deal?
Yeah, fine.
But if we're going there,
we're not just bringing food.
The police thinks that the
murders was premeditated.
That's why they're looking at us.
Alright, let them look.
They'll see that you put what happened
behind you and you've moved on.
You know it hasn't been that easy.
Going to therapy isn't
a strike against you.
You need a lot to overcome.
I still am overcoming it.
It's not gonna make anybody think
that you're capable of murder.
No, this might.
What is this?
It's a paper that I wrote
my sophomore year at Georgetown.
'Each of us had to do a case
study on a unique murder'
'and I did mine on a woman who was killed'
'on her wedding night.'
Did you know that it's human
instinct to go head first
when you leap to your death?
- No.
- 'Well, it is.'
(Spencer) 'And later on,
they discovered that her neck'
was broken before she fell.
She was found holding her bridal bouquet
and her fingernails were wiped clean.
- What class was this for?
- It's for criminology.
Look, that's exactly the
way that Charlotte died.
What if somebody knows
that I wrote this paper
they know my history here and
they're trying to set me up?
Spence, breathe.
Being back here is making you paranoid.
Nobody's trying to hurt you, okay?
I'm telling you...
This is all just one big coincidence.
I don't think the police
are gonna see it that way.
[intense music]
You told me you had a
relationship with this person.
Ezra Fitz was my high
school English teacher.
And he told you he's gonna
give the advance back?
Well... he said he's thinking about it.
You heard about what
happened to his girlfriend.
He's not in a good place right now.
No writer is ever in a good place, Aria.
I thought the teacher
angle would help but perhaps
that's the problem.
Maybe Fitz isn't taking you seriously
'because you were his student.'
Liam, I want you to take over.
- Take over?
- Uh...
Jillian, it's not Aria's fault.
'She went to testify at this hearing'
'and there was a
murder in this town... '
Liam's right.
I just, I got really distracted
but it won't happen again.
Jillian, I know this author.
I can get through to him
better than anyone else.
This isn't personal, Aria.
I just want somebody to bring
back the book we paid for.
Liam, you can stay.
[dramatic music]
[instrumental music]
- Hey, Sabrina.
- Hey, hi.
- Do you have a sec?
- Sure.
Um, Ezra says that you
manage the place now.
He put me in charge when he
and Nicole went to Colombia.
They thought it'd be a month long thing.
Hell of a way to get promoted.
Yeah. Well, I won't keep you.
I just wanted to stop
by and ask you a favor.
Sure.
Um... could you not tell anyone
that you saw me outside at
the medical center today?
I'm not quite sure who I would tell.
I know, it's just my
mom comes here sometimes
and my friends and...
Yeah. I won't say anything.
Thanks.
Emily...
I had cancer...
Several years ago.
I didn't want people to know.
I didn't want them to think of me
as the sick girl with cancer.
But I learned the hard way you need support
when you're going through
something like that.
I don't know what I would
have done without my family
my friends.
I don't wanna make assumptions
about what you're going through.
No, I'm, I'm sorry, you
had to deal with that
but I'm fine.
And the last thing I need to do...
Is to give my mom
something else to worry about.
Okay.
- Hi.
- Oh, wow.
- You guys bring enough food?
- Oh, there's more.
Hey, Hanna. Hi, Jordan.
- 'Hey, Jordan.'
- 'Hey.'
- 'So good to see you.'
- You too.
Uh, Jordan, this is Caleb. Caleb, Jordan.
I finally get to meet the Caleb Rivers.
Yeah, it's nice to meet you.
Any chance you wanna help me get
the last load of food from the car?
Uh, yeah. How much did you guys bring?
[chuckles] I know. I
come from a big family.
Always over-order.
[instrumental music]
They'll be fine.
- How are you doing?
- I'm holding up, I guess.
I'm glad everyone could make it...
Except for Aria.
Has anyone talked to her?
Uh, not since she left.
Yeah, I've called her a few times.
She hasn't returned my calls.
She's probably just busy with work.
What are you doing?
I was just gonna make some room.
I bought those for Charlotte
to welcome her home.
(Emily) Spence.
Okay. Well, then the
flowers can stay there.
I'll go get some serving spoons.
[music continues]
[sighs]
That was weird.
[whispering] Yeah,
maybe she knows about us.
This is her way of pitting
us against each other.
I don't know. I think
she just wants her pages.
We can figure this out.
If Fitz isn't taking you
seriously, then I'll go...
That's not the issue.
Then-then what is?
Aria.
Wh-what's going on?
[instrumental music]
Ezra Fitz is not the
same person that you met
on his book tour two years ago.
But I am gonna talk to Jillian
and I'm gonna convince her
to give me another shot.
Yeah, you should.
Just duck if she picks up the phone, okay?
[music continues]
[sighs]
- For how long?
- 'Couple of weeks.'
Maybe a month.
My mom asked me to stick around
for a while.
The Salk Institute won't mind?
No.
What do you do there?
Um, we research cures.
Alzheimer's, diabetes
infectious diseases.
Damn.
Well, you'll save 'em, I'll dress 'em.
Oh, perfect.
And I think it goes in this way.
[exhales deeply]
God, there's four bottles of wine
and nobody can find a wine opener.
This is not happening.
Uh, it's actually, it's backwards.
I used to have one just like it.
You kinda have to angle the leaves down.
Oh, the one with the scratch on it?
Yeah, it's the first piece of furniture
we put into the new place.
Hanna wouldn't let go of it.
- Caleb?
- Yeah.
Um, I can't find any wine glasses.
You wanna go check the pantry for me?
Yeah.
Nice.
So do you and Caleb see
much of each other in DC?
Uh, yeah, we do.
I mean, I don't really see much
of anybody except for my phone.
But of all the people that I don't see
I don't see Caleb the most.
Or the least.
Uh, it's nice you keep in contact.
I barely see any of my
friends from high school.
Oh, we didn't, uh, for a while.
And then we ran into each other in Madrid.
It was crazy. It was a total fluke.
I was just finishing my year abroad
and he was backpacking through Europe.
I was about to get on a train in Salamanca
and I heard my name and I looked up
and he was just standing there
on the opposite platform.
Wow. That sounds amazing.
Yeah, it was.
Oh, hey.
Hi.
Have you seen any wine glasses?
Ali de-boozifed the place when she thought
Charlotte was coming home.
But I'll help you find the wine glasses
if you help me find an opener.
Deal.
[music continues]
Jordan seems nice.
He is.
Uh, congrats on your engagement.
I-I meant to say that yesterday. Sorry.
Thank you.
- So you kept the table?
- Of course, I did.
[music continues]
Look, when you left for Europe...
I wanted to focus on my career.
I wasn't looking for another relationship.
You seem happy.
I am.
I'm glad.
[instrumental music]
Uh, found them.
Looks like we got what we need.
(Alison) 'Thank you. I, uh,
I appreciate you calling.'
Ali, who was that?
Lorenzo. He said he'd
call with any updates.
- What was it? The update?
- Time of death.
Charlotte was killed around 4:00 a.m.
Are you okay?
Lorenzo says this is good news.
They're one step closer
to finding her killer.
Let's say grace.
Hanna, hand.
Thank you, Heavenly Father
for this healing food
and these dear friends
and thank you to all those
who are working tirelessly
'to seek justice for Charlotte.'
And thank you for helping the
police find Charlotte's killer
and anyone who could be
protecting him or her.
'Thank you always for
your guidance and love.'
Amen.
(all) 'Amen.'
[intense music]
[sighs] That was awkward.
Was that speech directed at us?
Not at us but... Aria maybe.
Why would Ali think that
Aria had anything to do
with Charlotte's death?
Maybe she did.
Aria left the hotel the
night that she was killed.
- How do you know this?
- I saw her.
She left around 3:00 a.m. and
I don't know when she got back.
- Let's just ask her.
- Well, I tried that.
She denied going anywhere but her car.
Okay, well, there are
surveillance cameras, right
in the lobby of the hotel?
- Yeah.
- Your mom's the manager.
So maybe you could find a way
to get a look at the
footage from that night.
No. I'm don't do stuff like that anymore.
Hanna, I know it's a lot to ask, okay?
But how else are we supposed to make sure
that Aria came back before Charlotte died?
[intense music]
How's Alison doin'?
Um, she's dealing... in her own Ali way.
Well, I'm sure it helps having you around.
Showing there's a light
at the end of the tunnel.
[cellphone vibrates]
Hollis Medical Center? Wait,
you have an appointment?
Um...
- Are you feeling okay?
- I'm fine.
I-it's just an interview, um...
For grad school.
Grad school at Hollis?
Oh, why didn't you tell
me you were applying?
I'm just exploring my options.
I mean, honestly it's...
The institute just
wanted me to look into it.
Wow.
Okay.
So what are you thinking?
I mean, you've always
talked about sports medicine.
You know who you should
talk to? Aunt Kathy.
She's a nurse practitioner.
- Right?
- Here you go, ladies.
Let me know if you need anything else.
You know, honey, if you're
worried about paying for it
you shouldn't be.
Dad left you all that money
for exactly this reason
and you can just take
out a loan for the rest.
You know, all the work you're doing
the person you've become
your dad would be really
proud of you, Emmy.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[instrumental music]
[knock on door]
Hey.
(Ezra) I wasn't expecting anyone.
I thought you went back to Boston.
I did.
I flew back to talk to you.
Oh! Well, you could've called.
My boss has this thing
about how it's harder
to say no in person.
This is about the book.
Drink?
No, thank you.
They won't take back the advance.
Ah! So they are mad.
N-not mad.
They just loved "Ostinato."
Well, it made them money.
It made them feel things.
It's a really good book, Ezra
and I am not just saying
that to flatter you. It is.
I promise you they are not
going to love the follow-up.
(Aria) 'That's it? That's the book?'
It's as far as I got.
Can I look at it?
Hey, first draft is a first draft.
I'm sure it's not that bad.
[intense music]
That night after we saw each other
after I went back to the
hotel where did you go?
What are you asking me?
You know what I'm asking you.
Where did you go?
[music continues]
Home, Aria.
I went home.
[music continues]
Spence, stop worrying about the paper.
You gotta let it go.
Are you sure you're okay
sleeping on the couch again?
Yeah, totally.
It's a lot more comfortable
than those hostel beds in Europe.
Can you believe that it's been three years
since we were in Madrid?
[chuckles] That's crazy.
I don't think I'm ever gonna forgive you
for dragging me to that awful bullfight.
Come on, it was not that awful.
It-it was awful when you started screaming
"Savages" at the drunk crowd.
It was terrible from the beginning.
That's why I was screaming.
- It was awful.
- 'Okay.'
- You made me cry.
- I didn't make you do anything.
You didn't stop me from
crying in the street.
You were, you were pretty livid.
It was not okay.
But, hey, I redeemed myself
when I snuck us into Retiro Park
with a couple bottles of Sangria.
Yeah, you did.
[chuckles]
Oh, my God, that was the
most beautiful sunrise.
Yeah.
It was my best night in Europe.
[instrumental music]
Mine too. Hands down.
Yeah.
[music continues]
Uh, hey, your mom asked me to...
Stick around and help with the campaign.
That's a great idea.
[cellphone beeps]
[music continues]
Let me know if you need anything.
Thank you.
(Emily) 'Where does Jordan think you are?'
(Hanna) 'Talking to my mom.'
There she is.
(Hanna) 'It's 3:12.'
What the hell was Ezra doing there?
So much for just going to her car.
[door opens]
Hey, the hallway's clear
but there's a cleaning crew
down the hall.
- Okay, hurry.
- I'm going as fast as I can.
- What did I miss?
- Aria left the hotel with Ezra.
What?
But she didn't come back with him.
[intense music]
'It's 4:28.'
What time did Ali say
that Charlotte was killed?
Close to 4:00.
'Just because she came back
after the time of murder'
it doesn't mean that she
had anything to do with it.
No, but it doesn't look good.
What do we do?
Do we erase the video?
We're not in high school, Emily.
We're gonna talk to Aria.
She won't tell us anything.
(Spencer) 'Well, she doesn't
have a choice this time.'
[dramatic music]
How did you know I was back?
I saw you visiting Ezra.
We know you saw him the
night Charlotte died.
We know you left the hotel
for more than five minutes.
Yeah, and by the time you came
back Charlotte was already dead.
It's time to tell us what
really happened that night.
You didn't have to come by.
Well, you said you couldn't sleep.
Ugh, I can't.
I just keep going over
what I said to the judge.
God, that look on Ali's face.
Look, what you said
was honest and brave.
So if your friends are
giving you a hard time...
No, no, no, no.
They're not... at all.
They'd actually wish that
they'd said the same thing.
I mean, that's the crazy part.
I-I just thought if one of us had said no
then that would just be the end of it.
Yeah, me too.
Hey, can we go somewhere?
Anywhere but here.
Of course.
[instrumental music]
(Aria) Mm, why is everything closed?
It's suburban Pennsylvania
and about 4:00 a.m.
Yeah, I want pizza.
Doesn't anybody care that I want pizza?
You know, I know this little...
Bookstore cafe around the corner.
It's closed, but I
happen to know the owner.
[chuckles]
No, no, I should go. It's late.
Yeah, sure.
(Aria) 'Is that Alison?'
'Looks like her car.'
I think that's Charlotte.
Do we call someone? Do we call the police?
No, Aria. She's free now.
It's her town now as much as ours.
Oh, she's free and she's
already lurking in the shadows.
'Why the hell is she not home with Ali?'
(Ezra) 'Cause that's the
kind of world we live in.
People like Nicole disappear
and Charlotte gets to walk free.
Ezra.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah. You know, it's-it's getting late.
You should probably get back to your hotel.
Yeah.
Goodnight.
[dramatic music]
He told me he went home afterwards.
But... I don't know.
He-he was so angry.
- Aria, what is it?
- I know him.
And I know that Ezra can't
look me in the eye when he lies.
And when he told me he
went home, he didn't...
Look at me.
[sighs] Well, we have to tell someone.
- Lorenzo, Ali, anyone.
- No, we don't.
Now, this is a giant leap.
We're talking about Ezra killing someone.
I mean, until we have actual proof
we don't tell anyone anything.
It's not.
[music continues]
It's not a giant leap.
In fact, I think I told Ezra how to do it.
Ezra was on his book tour and
we got together for lunch.
He was still trying to
figure out what he wanted
to write next and he said
that he was toying around
with the idea of a murder mystery.
I had just written my paper so I told him
about the case in detail.
Maybe Ezra did do this to protect you.
Protect me?
By copying some bizarre
murder from the past?
Spencer, this was a public case.
You weren't the only two who knew about it.
He saw how upset Aria was in the courtroom.
And he's still angry about
what happened to Nicole.
I mean, who knows what he's capable of now?
If he did kill Charlotte
and the police find out...
It's gonna look like
you were involved too.
You left the hotel with Ezra
and you came back a half hour
after Charlotte was killed.
Nobody can see that security footage.
[dramatic music]
Why did you show this to me?
I wanted you to know that I wrote it.
Somebody from my class could remember it
and read about Charlotte
and connect the dots.
What dots?
Do you know anything about
what happened to Charlotte?
- No.
- Then I'm not worried.
Mom, how can you not worry?
If this gets out, it's
going to ruin your campaign
if I haven't done
that already...
You haven't. And it won't.
- We'll get ahead of this.
- How?
Caleb already started a narrative
about you being bullied on social media.
If this comes up, it'll
already be diffused.
You are not a liability, Spencer.
You're my daughter.
[instrumental music]
(Emily) 'I was in class
when Mom called the school.'
Human anatomy.
Everything we went through in high school...
I thought we were done with disasters.
[sighs] The next semester...
Nothing made sense anymore.
Um, if you really are
watching over me, then...
I guess you know this already.
I flunked two classes and...
They took my scholarship away.
After that, I, I couldn't go back there.
I flew home that summer
and I was, was ready
to tell Mom about everything but...
She was such a mess.
And I couldn't do it.
[sniffles]
[sobbing] I know... that I messed up...
Okay, but I'm going to fix it.
I am fixing it.
[twig snaps]
[dramatic music]
[gasps]
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
[keyboard keys clanking]
♪ And blessed are those ♪
♪ Who see and are silent ♪
♪ Blessed are those ♪
♪ Blessed are those... ♪
[cellphone vibrates]
♪ See and are silent ♪
♪ Blessed are those ♪
♪ Who see ♪
♪ So won't you hoist up ♪
♪ The bucket now Charlie ♪
♪ Mud marks up to our necks ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ And they did unfold ♪
♪ And the wind it did fill them ♪
♪ And they did unfold and the wind... ♪
[instrumental music]
Everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[music continues]
Thank you for coming over.
Ali, what's this about?
Last night you asked me
if I thought my friends
had anything to do with Charlotte's murder.
Do you wanna change your answer?
Yes.
♪ It bashes us in ♪
♪ Bashes us about a bit ♪
♪ Feel it tugging you ♪
♪ Ploughing you flat ♪
♪ Then feel it filling your sails ♪
♪ And warm on your back ♪
I'm sorry for your loss.
[music continues]
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com